

London, United Kingdom

□ (+44) 7928148339 | agustibau@gmail.com | □ ihatetothink

Summary _

I'm a software engineer with about 3 years of experience. I've spent most of my time developing **backend** systems. I would say that my best asset is that I'm an avid and **quick learner**. Among professional experience and personal projects, I have experience in **Java**, **nodejs**, **postgres**, **mongoDB**, **redis**, **android**, **react**, **react native**, **some pytorch and tensorflow** (in order of familiarity). I'm always eager to learn new technologies and I try to have at least a basic understanding of what different technologies enable us to do. I'm usually tinkering around and I always have a personal project in my burner. I love how technology is able to shape the world and I enjoy solving the problems in doing so. Between DataTiger and Zinc, I did take a sabbatical year traveling around east Europe. Now I'm ready to kick ass.

Experience _

Misison3 - Entrepreneur London

Zinc.vc Sept. 2019 - present

Social startup incubator with a social focus. I researched few ideas in the clinical trial space. Developed relationships with knowledgeable people in the field and developed a few prototypes (react, react native, nodejs). We haven't found proper product-market fit and constrains are tight. Learnt how to develop prototypes in a quickly manner, and improved my people skills.

Software engineer London

Data Tiger Oct. 2017 - Oct. 2018

Joined in the early stages of the start-up (8Th hire), developed multiple parts of the system alongside tools to improve our workflow. The tool we built was following a microsevices architecture using Java, python, Sql, Docker, AWS. Provided an horizontally scalable solution to ingest events from different sources and allow marketeers to define user specific marketing actions to be performed in accordance to those events. I was responsible for big parts of:

- Analytics system based on a data lake architecture
- Fail resilent GDPR service responsible for deleting data and marking users that requested so
- Multiple integrations with different systems (email providers, other event providers, ad networks, among others)

Junior software engineer

Barcelona

Jun. 2016 - Sept. 2018

Joined as an intern during summer 2016, then got hired as a full-time backend developer of a marketing internal system. It was basically a segmentation system based on Amazon Redshift, a couple of ETL processes and a Kafka integration. We develop using agile methodologies a backend built with Java on top of JBoss in a monolith fashion. It had many issues due it's messy evolution over time, and most of the work was to maintain said system.

Personal Project. Developer - Product design - Everything

Remote for Mac Mar. 2013

Android app that lets you control your OSX device from your android phone, without the need of any server-side software or hardware accessories, got around 200k downloads.

Education _____

Barcelona School of Informatics

Barcelona, Spain

Bachelor Degree in Computer Science and Engineering with Computer Engineering Specialization. Avg: 7.32 (out of 10)

2012 - 2018

Languages ___

English

All my professional career has been in English speaking companies and so I can confidently say, I'm able to communicate effectively in a professional environment

Catalan and Spanish

Mother Tongue

AGUSTI BAU · 1